open cupboards
take out Tupperware
turn on tap
pick up whetstone
place whetstone in Tupperware
adjust tap
test water
turn off tap
pick up whetstone
place down in Tupperware
pick up knife
pick up paper
test knife
take out whetstone
shake off whetstone
pick up knife
ford sharpening
sharpening
apply water
change blade angle
change blade sides
sharpening
apply water
change site
sharpening
apply water
change side
sharpening
shake off blade
wipeoff blade
put down blade
put back cloth
pick up blade
test blade
test blade on paper
put down blade
pick up topperware
empty water
put on dryrack
pick up sharpening stem
shakeoff sharpening stem
rinse sharpening stem
Rinse sharpening stand
Shake off sharpening stand
Place sharpening stand on counter
Pick up sharpening guide
Wash
Dry
Place on dry rack
Shake off hands
Pick up knife
Shake off knife
Put away knife
[END SUBTITLE]